Finding Aid for the University of Tennessee Theatre Collection, 1901- AR.0235
University of Tennessee Libraries, Special Collections
- Plays, 1941 February 18-2010 December 2-19; I; (Playbills, Photographs, Press Clippings, Production Materials, Posters, Stage Designs, and Scrapbooks)
  - Individual Plays, 1941 February 18-2010 December 19; A; (Playbills, Photographs, Press Clippings, Production Materials, Posters, Stage Designs, and Scrapbooks)
    - The Man Who Came to Dinner (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1987 October 2-17; (3 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - The Man Who Came to Dinner (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1987 October 2-17; (4 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - The Man Who Came to Dinner (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1987 October 2-17; (5 of 5); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - The Miss Firecracker Contest (Carousel Theatre), 1987 October 23-November 7; (1 of 6); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - The Miss Firecracker Contest (Carousel Theatre), 1987 October 23-November 7; (2 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - The Miss Firecracker Contest (Carousel Theatre), 1987 October 23-November 7; (3 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 12, Folder 71)
    - The Miss Firecracker Contest (Carousel Theatre), 1987 October 23-November 7; (4 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 12, Folder 72)
    - The Miss Firecracker Contest (Carousel Theatre), 1987 October 23-November 7; (5 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - The Miss Firecracker Contest (Carousel Theatre), 1987 October 23-November 7; (6 of 6); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - Pygmalion (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1987 November 27-December 19; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 12, Folder 75)
    - Pygmalion (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1987 November 27-December 19; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 12, Folder 76)
    - Pygmalion (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1987 November 27-December 19; (3 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 12, Folder 77)
    - Pygmalion (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1987 November 27-December 19; (4 of 4); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 12, Folder 78)
    - Little Women (Carousel Theatre), 1987 December 18-19; (1 of 4); (Programs and Press Clippings) (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - Little Women (Carousel Theatre), 1987 December 18-19; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - Little Women (Carousel Theatre), 1987 December 18-19; (3 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - Little Women (Carousel Theatre), 1987 December 18-19; (4 of 4); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - Master Harold and the Boys (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1988 January 29-February 13; (1 of 6); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - Master Harold and the Boys (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1988 January 29-February 13; (2 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - Master Harold and the Boys (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1988 January 29-February 13; (3 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 12, Folder 85)
    - Master Harold and the Boys (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1988 January 29-February 13; (4 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 12, Folder 86)
    - Master Harold and the Boys (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1988 January 29-February 13; (5 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 12, Folder 87)
    - Master Harold and the Boys (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1988 January 29-February 13; (6 of 6); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 12, Folder 88)
    - The Seagull, circa 1988 February-March; (1 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - The Seagull, circa 1988 February-March; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - To Clothe the Naked (Carousel Theatre), 1988 February 19-March 5; (1 of 6); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - To Clothe the Naked (Carousel Theatre), 1988 February 19-March 5; (2 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - To Clothe the Naked (Carousel Theatre), 1988 February 19-March 5; (3 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - To Clothe the Naked (Carousel Theatre), 1988 February 19-March 5; (4 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - To Clothe the Naked (Carousel Theatre), 1988 February 19-March 5; (5 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - To Clothe the Naked (Carousel Theatre), 1988 February 19-March 5; (6 of 6); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Uncommon Women (Clarence Brown Studio Theatre), 1988 March 3-5; (1 of 2); (Press Clippings) (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Uncommon Women (Clarence Brown Studio Theatre), 1988 March 3-5; (2 of 2); (Production Materials) (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - The Diary of Anne Frank (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1988 March 18-April 1; (1 of 7); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - The Diary of Anne Frank (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1988 March 18-April 1; (2 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - The Diary of Anne Frank (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1988 March 18-April 1; (3 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - The Diary of Anne Frank (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1988 March 18-April 1; (4 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - The Diary of Anne Frank (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1988 March 18-April 1; (5 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - The Diary of Anne Frank (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1988 March 18-April 1; (6 of 7); (Production Materials) (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - The Diary of Anne Frank (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1988 March 18-April 1; (7 of 7); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Man of Mode (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1988 April 8-23; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Man of Mode (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1988 April 8-23; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Man of Mode (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1988 April 8-23; (3 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Man of Mode (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1988 April 8-23; (4 of 4); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - On the Verge (Carousel Theatre), 1988 May 13-28; (1 of 3); (Playbills) (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - On the Verge (Carousel Theatre), 1988 May 13-28; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - On the Verge (Carousel Theatre), 1988 May 13-28; (3 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - The Pajama Game (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1988 May 27-June 18; (1 of 3); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - The Pajama Game (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1988 May 27-June 18; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - The Pajama Game (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1988 May 27-June 18; (3 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Amadeus (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1988 September 9-24; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Amadeus (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1988 September 9-24; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - The Crucible (Carousel Theatre), 1988 September 30-October 15; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - The Crucible (Carousel Theatre), 1988 September 30-October 15; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - The Threepenny Opera, circa 1988 October-November; (1 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - The Threepenny Opera, circa 1988 October-November; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - The Threepenny Opera, circa 1988 October-November; (3 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Uncle Vanya (Carousel Theatre), 1988 November 4-19; (1 of 3); (Playbills) (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Uncle Vanya (Carousel Theatre), 1988 November 4-19; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Uncle Vanya (Carousel Theatre), 1988 November 4-19; (3 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Deja Vu (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1989 February 3-18; (1 of 3); (Playbills) (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Deja Vu (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1989 February 3-18; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Deja Vu (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1989 February 3-18; (3 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Hunting Cockroaches (Carousel Theatre), 1989 February 23-March 4; (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Noises Off (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1989 March 31-April 15; (1 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Noises Off (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1989 March 31-April 15; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Cloud 9 (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1989 April 20-29; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Cloud 9 (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1989 April 20-29; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - A Little Night Music (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1989 June 2-24; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - A Little Night Music (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1989 June 2-24; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Camille (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1989 September 8-23; (1 of 3); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Camille (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1989 September 8-23; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Camille (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1989 September 8-23; (3 of 3); (Negatives) (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Ceremonies in Dark Old Men (Carousel Theatre), 1989 September 28-October 7; (1 of 3); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Ceremonies in Dark Old Men (Carousel Theatre), 1989 September 28-October 7; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Ceremonies in Dark Old Men (Carousel Theatre), 1989 September 28-October 7; (3 of 3); (Production Materials) (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Crimes of the Heart (Carousel Theatre), 1989 November 3-18; (1 of 4); (Playbills, Mailers, and Press Clippings) (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Crimes of the Heart (Carousel Theatre), 1989 November 3-18; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Crimes of the Heart (Carousel Theatre), 1989 November 3-18; (3 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Crimes of the Heart (Carousel Theatre), 1989 November 3-18; (4 of 4); (Financial Materials) (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Heathen Valley (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1990 February 2-17; (1 of 3); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Heathen Valley (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1990 February 2-17; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Heathen Valley (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1990 February 2-17; (3 of 3); (Production Materials) (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - The Winter's Tale (Carousel Theatre), 1990 February 23-March 10; (1 of 3); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - The Winter's Tale (Carousel Theatre), 1990 February 23-March 10; (2 of 3); (Negatives) (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - The Winter's Tale (Carousel Theatre), 1990 February 23-March 10; (3 of 3); (Production Materials) (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - On Golden Pond (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1990 March 30-April 14; (1 of 5); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - On Golden Pond (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1990 March 30-April 14; (2 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - On Golden Pond (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1990 March 30-April 14; (3 of 5); (Negatives) (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - On Golden Pond (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1990 March 30-April 14; (4 of 5); (Negatives) (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - On Golden Pond (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1990 March 30-April 14; (5 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - Aunt Dan and Lemon (Carousel Theatre), 1990 April 19-28; (1 of 3); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Aunt Dan and Lemon (Carousel Theatre), 1990 April 19-28; (2 of 3); (Photographs/Negatives) (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - Aunt Dan and Lemon (Carousel Theatre), 1990 April 19-28; (3 of 3); (Production Materials) (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - Nine (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1990 June 1-16; (1 of 3); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - Nine (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1990 June 1-16; (2 of 3); (Negatives) (Box 13, Folder 73)
    - Nine (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1990 June 1-16; (3 of 3); (Production Materials) (Box 13, Folder 74)
    - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1990 July 27-August 4; (Playbills) (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Steel Magnolias (Carousel Theatre), 1990 October 4-21; (1 of 3); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Steel Magnolias (Carousel Theatre), 1990 October 4-21; (2 of 3); (Negatives) (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Steel Magnolias (Carousel Theatre), 1990 October 4-21; (3 of 3); (Production Materials) (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - To Kill a Mockingbird (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1990 October 16-18, 23-25; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - To Kill a Mockingbird (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1990 October 16-18, 23-25; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - To Kill a Mockingbird (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1990 October 16-18, 23-25; (3 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - To Kill a Mockingbird (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1990 October 16-18, 23-25; (4 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Blood Relations, 1990 October 31-November 17; (1 of 2); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Blood Relations, 1990 October 31-November 17; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - A Christmas Carol (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1990 November 23-December 6, 15-22; (1 of 3); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - A Christmas Carol (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1990 November 23-December 6, 15-22; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - A Christmas Carol (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1990 November 23-December 6, 15-22; (3 of 3); (Production Materials) (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Mr. Roosevelt's Train Never Got Here (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1991 February 1-16; (1 of 6); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Mr. Roosevelt's Train Never Got Here (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1991 February 1-16; (2 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Mr. Roosevelt's Train Never Got Here (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1991 February 1-16; (3 of 6); (Negatives) (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Mr. Roosevelt's Train Never Got Here (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1991 February 1-16; (4 of 6); (Negatives) (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Mr. Roosevelt's Train Never Got Here (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1991 February 1-16; (5 of 6); (Negatives) (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Mr. Roosevelt's Train Never Got Here (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1991 February 1-16; (6 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Blood Wedding (Carousel Theatre), 1991 February 22-March 9; (1 of 2); (Playbill and Press Clippings) (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Blood Wedding (Carousel Theatre), 1991 February 22-March 9; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - The Marriage of Bette and Boo (Carousel Theatre), 1991 March 1-16; (1 of 2); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - The Marriage of Bette and Boo (Carousel Theatre), 1991 March 1-16; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - The Skin of Our Teeth (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1991 April 11-27; (1 of 2); (Playbill and PSA) (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - The Skin of Our Teeth (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1991 April 11-27; (2 of 2); (Negatives) (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Into the Woods (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1991 May 30-June 15; (Playbills) (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - When the Nightengale Sings (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1991 September 6-22; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - When the Nightengale Sings (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1991 September 6-22; (2 of 2); (Negatives) (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - The Heidi Chronicles (Carousel Theatre), 1991 October 11-27; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - The Heidi Chronicles (Carousel Theatre), 1991 October 11-27; (2 of 2); (Negatives) (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Fan Shen, 1991 November 7-17; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Fan Shen, 1991 November 7-17; (2 of 2); (Negatives) (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - A Christmas Carol (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1991 November 22-December 22; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - A Christmas Carol (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1991 November 22-December 22; (2 of 2); (Production Materials) (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - I'm Not Rappaport (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1992 February 7-23; (Playbills) (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Masque of Grace (Clarence Brown Lab Theatre), 1992 February 13-29; (Playbills) (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Twelfth Night (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1992 March 6-21; (Playbills) (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - 1776 (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1992 April 10-26; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - 1776 (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1992 April 10-26; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Les Liaisons Dangereuses (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1992 June 5-21; (Playbills) (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - A Man for All Seasons (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1992 September 11-October 3; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - A Man for All Seasons (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1992 September 11-October 3; (2 of 2); (Production Materials) (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - The Mandrake (Clarence Brown Lab Theatre), 1992 October 2-16; (Playbills) (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - A Shayna Maidel (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1992 October 30-November 15; (Playbills) (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Oliver! (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1992 November 20-December 13; (Playbill) (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Man and Superman (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 January 29-February 14; (1 of 5); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Man and Superman (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 January 29-February 14; (2 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Man and Superman (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 January 29-February 14; (3 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Man and Superman (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 January 29-February 14; (4 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Man and Superman (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 January 29-February 14; (5 of 5); (Financial Materials) (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Psycho Beach Party (Carousel Theatre), 1993 February 18-March 6; (1 of 3); (Playbills, Flyers, and Press Clippings) (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Psycho Beach Party (Carousel Theatre), 1993 February 18-March 6; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Psycho Beach Party (Carousel Theatre), 1993 February 18-March 6; (3 of 3); (Production Materials) (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Lilliom (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 April 16-May 2; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Lilliom (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 April 16-May 2; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Lilliom (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 April 16-May 2; (3 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Lilliom (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 April 16-May 2; (4 of 4); (Financial Materials) (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Driving Miss Daisy (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 June 4-20; (Playbills) (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - The Music Man (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 July 9-August 1; (1 of 4); (Press Clippings) (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - The Music Man (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 July 9-August 1; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - The Music Man (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 July 9-August 1; (3 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - The Music Man (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 July 9-August 1; (4 of 4); (Financial Materials) (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - I Hate Hamlet (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 August 27-September 12; (1 of 5); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - I Hate Hamlet (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 August 27-September 12; (2 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - I Hate Hamlet (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 August 27-September 12; (3 of 5); (Negatives) (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - I Hate Hamlet (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 August 27-September 12; (4 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - I Hate Hamlet (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 August 27-September 12; (5 of 5); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - The Cowboy Comedy of Errors (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 October 1-17; (1 of 6); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - The Cowboy Comedy of Errors (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 October 1-17; (2 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - The Cowboy Comedy of Errors (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 October 1-17; (3 of 6); (Negatives) (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - The Cowboy Comedy of Errors (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 October 1-17; (4 of 6); (Negatives) (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - The Cowboy Comedy of Errors (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 October 1-17; (5 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - The Cowboy Comedy of Errors (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 October 1-17; (6 of 6); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 14, Folder 73)
    - The Secret Rapture (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1993 October 29-November 13; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 14, Folder 74)
    - The Secret Rapture (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1993 October 29-November 13; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 14, Folder 75)
    - The Secret Rapture (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1993 October 29-November 13; (3 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 14, Folder 76)
    - The Secret Rapture (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1993 October 29-November 13; (4 of 4); (Financial Materials) (Box 14, Folder 77)
    - The 1940s Radio Hour (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 November 19-December 12; (1 of 5); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 14, Folder 78)
    - The 1940s Radio Hour (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 November 19-December 12; (2 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 14, Folder 79)
    - The 1940s Radio Hour (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 November 19-December 12; (3 of 5); (Negatives) (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - The 1940s Radio Hour (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 November 19-December 12; (4 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - The 1940s Radio Hour (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1993 November 19-December 12; (5 of 5); (Financial Materials) (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Our Country's Good (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 February 4-20; (1 of 5); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Our Country's Good (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 February 4-20; (2 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Our Country's Good (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 February 4-20; (3 of 5); (Negatives) (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Our Country's Good (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 February 4-20; (4 of 5); (Negatives) (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Our Country's Good (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 February 4-20; (5 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Top Girls (Ula Love Doughty Theatre), 1994 March 11-19; (1 of 3); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Top Girls (Ula Love Doughty Theatre), 1994 March 11-19; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Top Girls (Ula Love Doughty Theatre), 1994 March 11-19; (3 of 3); (Production Materials) (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - The Royal Hunt of the Sun (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 April 15-May 1; (1 of 5); (Playbills, Postcards, and Press Clippings) (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - The Royal Hunt of the Sun (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 April 15-May 1; (2 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - The Royal Hunt of the Sun (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 April 15-May 1; (3 of 5); (Negatives) (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - The Royal Hunt of the Sun (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 April 15-May 1; (4 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - The Royal Hunt of the Sun (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 April 15-May 1; (5 of 5); (Financial Materials) (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - A Funny Thing Happened On the Way to the Forum (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 May 27-June 12; (1 of 6); (Playbills, Flyers, and Press Clippings) (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - A Funny Thing Happened On the Way to the Forum (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 May 27-June 12; (2 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 15, Folder 18)